billhicksco.com 2014-12-08

# Infor ERP Storefront Commerce

## Privacy Policy

1.    **Introduction.  **Bill Hicks & Co., Ltd. ("Bill Hicks & Co." or "We") respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.  This policy describes the type of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.BillHicksCo.com **** (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.  Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time.  Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

2.    **Application**. This policy applies to information we collect on this Website, in e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website, or through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-brower-based interaction between you and this Website. This policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by a third party (including our affiliates), or any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website. 

3.    **Information We Collect About You.** We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

a.   by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address or telephone number ("Personal Information");

b.   that is about you but individually does not identify you, and/or

c.   about your internet connection, the equipment and software you use to access our Website and usage details.

4.     **How We Collect the Information.**  We collect this information:

a.    Directly from you when you provide it to us.

b.   Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.

5.    **Information You Provide to Us**. The information we collect on or through our Website may include, but is not limited to: 

a.   Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information such as when you enter a promotion sponsored by us, or when you report a problem with our Website.

b.   Records and copies of your correspondence, including e-mail addresses, if you contact us.

c.    Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.

d.   Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.

e.   Your search queries on the Website

6.    **User Contributions.**  You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, " **posted** ") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, " **User Contributions** "). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages and you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

7.    **Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies.** As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website, and information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. The information we collect helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service by enabling us to: estimate our audience size and usage patterns; store information about your preferences; customize our Website according to your individual interests; speed up your searches; and recognize you when you return to our Website. The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

a.   Cookies (or browser cookies), a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.

b.   Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.

c.    Web Beacons. Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as pixel tags) that permits us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

8.   **How We Use Your Information.  **We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information:

a.   To present our Website and its contents to you.

b.   To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.

c.   To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.

d.   To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.

e.   To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.

f.    To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.

g.   To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.

h.   In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

i.    For any other purpose with your consent.

j.    To contact you about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

9.  **Disclosure of Your Information**. We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We may disclose Personal Information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

a.   To our subsidiaries and affiliates.

b.   To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential.

c.   To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Bill Hicks & Co.’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Bill Hicks & Co. about our Website users is among the assets transferred.

d.   To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.

e.   For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

f.    With your consent.

g.   To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

h.   To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.

i.    If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Bill Hicks & Co., our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

10.  **Accessing and Correcting Your Information**. You can review and change your Personal Information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. You may also **send us an e-mail** to request access to, correct or delete any Personal Information that you have provided to us. We may not be able to delete your Personal Information without also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Use.

11.  **Data Security.**  We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transaction will be processed using secure, encrypted SSL technology. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. 

12.  **Changes to Our Privacy Policy.  **It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. You are responsible for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.
